AD.MC.028
AbuDhabi
- Men eating and drinking. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref973)
- Clergyman giving out a speech in school. 15.1 x 10.1 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref974)
  Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School events; Schools/Education
- Student giving out a speech in an honoring ceremony. 15.2 x 10.1 cm, 1988; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref975)
  Adolescents; Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Microphones; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trophies
- Students taking a group photo in front and behind a fence in school. 10.1 x 15.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref976)
  Boys; Fences; Group Portraits; Groups, Social; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Two men sitting on a desk. 14.8 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref977)
  Desks; Drinking; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Man and woman sitting on a desk. 15 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref978)
  Drinking; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Three men sitting in a room. 15 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref979)
  Drinking; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Windows
- Group photo of school staff. 14.9 x 10.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref980)
  Children; Drinks; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Food; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Women
- Al-Tewfiqi Mosque. 15 x 10.1 cm, 1884; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref981)
  Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Islamic Architecture; Minaret; Mosques; Photographic Prints
- Staff meeting in an office in school. 13.5 x 18.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref982)
  Awards; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Offices; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trophies
- Staff meeting in an office in school. 18 x 11.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref983)
- School building. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref984)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trees
- School class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref985)
  Boys; Clergymen; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Candid photo of students in school. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref986)
  Architecture; Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Trees
- Students playing football in a field. 4.1 x 6.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref987)
  Adolescents; Fields; Football; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Sports; Students
- Human pyramid in school. 9.7 x 14.2 cm, 1946; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref988)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Pyramids; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Sports
- A man with two clergymen. 5.5 x 5.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref989)
  Clergymen; Gardens; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints
- Student group photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref990)
  Adolescents; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education
- Boys taking a group photo. 6.2 x 9.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref991)
  Boys; Coats/Jackets; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Stairs; Students
- Three members of school staff in a candid photo. 7.4 x 10.7 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref992)
  Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Students taking a picture in Theatre day. 6.2 x 9 cm, 20/11/1948; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref993)
  Boys; Costumes; French Writing; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Theater
- School event. 8.9 x 13.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref994)
  Balcony/Terrace; Boys; Flags; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Nuns; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Women
- Students and teachers in a field trip(?). 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref995)
  Boys; Donkeys; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Students and teachers on field trip. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref996)
  Boys; Field-trip; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Woman sitting on bench during school trip. 13.9 x 9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref997)
  Boys; Field-trip; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees; Water; Women; Women's Clothing
- Individual portrait of high school student. 8.7 x 6 cm, 5 February 1978; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref998)
  Arabic Writing; Boys; Clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait at a school field trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref999)
  Boats/Ships; Boys; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Students; Teachers; Water
- Group portrait during a school trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1000)
  Boys; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Students; Teachers; Trees
- Group portrait during a field trip. 5.7 x 8.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1001)
  Boys; Donkeys; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Students; Teachers
- Two men during a field trip (?). 6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1002)
  Buildings; Clothing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trees
- Inside of a church. 8.8 x 6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1003)
  Architecture; Benches; Boys; Christians; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses
- Boys next to a tent in the desert. 6 x 8.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1004)
- Group portrait of a family. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1005)
  Family Portraits; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women; Women's Clothing
- Group portrait. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1006)
  Boys; Clothing; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Trees; Women
- Boys on paddle boats. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1007)
  Boats/Ships; Boys; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Parks; Photographic Prints; Students; Trees; Water
- Group portrait during field trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1008)
  Boys; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait during school trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1009)
  Boys; Buildings; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Boys on paddle boats. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1010)
  Boats/Ships; Boys; Buildings; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Groups, Social; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Students; Trees; Water
- Group portrait during field trip. 7.4 x 10.5 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1011)
  Boys; Buildings; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Hieroglyphic writing. 10.2 x 14.9 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1012)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints
- Individual portrait. 4.7 x 3.8 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1013)
  Christians; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education
- Individual portrait. 5 x 4.6 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1014)
  Beards; Christians; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education
- Individual portrait. 6.4 x 4.2 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1015)
  Christians; Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School uniforms; Schools/Education
- Individual portrait. 6.3 x 4.1 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1016)
  Beards; Christians; Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; Schools/Education
- Individual portrait. 6 x 3.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref1017)
- Postcard of the George Nuncovich hotels. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1890; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1018)
  Architecture; Camels; Donkeys; Egyptian clothing; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Hotels; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Postcards
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1019)
  Car accidents; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Women; Women's Clothing
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1020)
  Car accidents; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1021)
  Car accidents; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Women; Women's Clothing
- Car accident. 9 x 14 cm, 13 October 1979; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1022)
  Car accidents; Cars; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Inside a classroom with paintings and images on the wall. 8.8 x 12.9 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1023)
  Chairs; Classrooms; Color Photography; Helwan, Egypt; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Schools/Education; Tables
- Photo of the school's church taken on 1890. 8.9 x 12.6 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1024)
  Arabic Writing; Churches; Classrooms; Color Photography; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Ink-jet printing; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Schools/Education
- Map explaining the pharaonic typography for Helwan and neighboring regions. 10.6 x 8.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1025)
  Arabic Writing; Classrooms; Color Photography; Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Maps; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Teacher education
- Painting depicting ancient Egyptian deities Horus and Seth. 9.4 x 8.9 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1026)
  Arabic Writing; Classrooms; Color Photography; English Writing; God; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Photographs; Schools/Education
- Painting of Pharaoh Narmer's (or Menes) Palette in a classroom. 10.4 x 8.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1027)
  Arabic Writing; Art |x History; Classrooms; Color Photography; Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Helwan, Egypt; History; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education
- Painting illustrating an ancient Egyptian story (?). 9.9 x 8.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1028)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Arabic Writing; Classrooms; Color Photography; Egypt; English Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Paintings; Photographic Prints
- Painting of a map showing the location of Helwan. 10 x 8.8 cm, 1987; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1029)
  Arabic Writing; Art |x History; Classrooms; Color Photography; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; History; Italian Writing; Maps; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Water
- Church in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1890; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1030)
  Architecture; Christians; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
- Building in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1984; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1031)
  Buildings; Cars; Color Photography; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees; Women
- Group portrait of nuns. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1931; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1032)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; Schools/Education; Women; Women's Clothing
- Landscape of Helwan street. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1033)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Mosques; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1970; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1034)
  Girls; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Nuns; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Women; Women's Clothing
- Female students dressed in traditional Japanese kimono. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1947; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1035)
  Clothing; Costumes; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Umbrellas/Parasols
- Young girls in school dormitory. 9 x 13.9 cm, Undated; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1036)
  Beds; Dormitories; French Writing; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Nuns; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Students dressed in traditional clothing. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1037)
  Boys; Clothing; French Writing; Germany; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Traditional Dress
- Students on a bridge in the Japanese garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1917-1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1038)
  Boys; Bridges; Field-trip; Gardens; Girls; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Students; Trees; Water
- Group portrait of students on school trip to Japanese garden. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1917-1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1039)
  Boys; Field-trip; French Writing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students
- Group portrait on a beach. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1948; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1040)
  Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Students; Umbrellas/Parasols; Water
- Students on a rock posing. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1041)
  Boys; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Men; Photographic Prints; Rocks; Students; Teachers
- Landscape of the Japanese garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1917-1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1042)
  Field-trip; French Writing; Gardens; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Statues; Trees
- Students in the Japanese garden. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1917-1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1043)
  Boys; Field-trip; French Writing; Gardens; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Palm trees; Photographic Prints; Students; Trees
- Statues in the Japanese garden in Helwan. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1917-1920; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1044)
  Buildings; Field-trip; Gardens; Helwan, Egypt; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Statues; Trees; Water
- The school's church (?). 9 x 13.9 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1045)
  Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Trees
- Students and teachers in front of a bus. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1046)
  Boys; Buses; Field-trip; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1946; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1047)
  Architecture; Boys; Carpets/Rugs; Flags; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Sports team photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1048)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Sports teams; Students; Uniforms
- Students exercising. 9 x 13.9 cm, Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1049)
  Boys; Exercise; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers; Trees; Uniforms; Window Blinds; Windows
- Group portrait in front of statue. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1050)
  Ancient Egyptian Architecture; Boys; Field-trip; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Palm trees; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Statues; Students
- Field trip to Ain Helwan. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1051)
  Boys; Field-trip; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Springs; Students; Teachers; Water
- Helwan observatory. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1903; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1052)
  Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Observatory; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Window Blinds
- Students in theatrical costumes. 13.9 x 9 cm, 1910; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1053)
  Costumes; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Moustaches; Performance Plays; Photographic Prints; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Swords & Knives; Theater; Wigs
- Priests in front of cars. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1932; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1054)
  Cars; Deserts; Group Portraits; Hats; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education
- Group photo of students and teachers. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1935; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1055)
  Boys; Girls; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Class portrait. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1056)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1935; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1057)
  Advertisements; Beards; Clothing; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; Religious Crosses; School events; Schools/Education
- Class photo. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950-1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1058)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Priests; Religious Clothing; School events; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Group portrait. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1951; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1059)
  Boys; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Religious Clothing; School events; School uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Teachers
- Holy Family School. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1950; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1060)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Doors; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Streets/Roads; Window Blinds; Windows
- Photograph of a building. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1879; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1061)
  Architecture; Buildings; Cairo, Egypt; Doors; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Stairs
- Student dormitories. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1062)
  Beds; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Students; Window Blinds; Windows
- A photo of the Holy Family School. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1937; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1063)
  Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Trees; Windows
- Dining room. 9 x 13.9 cm, 1940; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1064)
  Cupboards; Helwan, Egypt; Interiors; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Plates; Schools/Education; Windows